Good morning. Mr. Croft.
早上好,Croft先生.
Good morning, nurse.
早上好,护士.
I want to see the dentist, please.
我想见牙科医生.
Do you have an appointment?
您约好了吗?
No, I don't.
没有.
Is it urgent?
急吗?
Yes, it is.
是的,
It's very urgent.
很急.
I feel awful.
我难受极了,
I have a terrible toothache.
牙痛得要命.
Can you come at 10 a. m. on Monday, April 24th?
您在4月24日星期一上午10点钟来行吗?
I must see the dentist now, nurse.
我必须现在就见牙科医生,护士.
The dentist is very busy at the moment.
牙科医生这会儿很忙.
Can you come at 2 p. m.?
您下午两点钟来行吗?
That's very late.
那就太晚了.
Can the dentist see me now?
牙科医生现在就不能给我看一下吗?
I'm afraid that he can't, Mr. Croft.
恐怕不能,克罗夫特先生.
Can't you wait till this afternoon?
您就不能等到今天下午吗?
I can wait, but my toothache can't!
我倒是可以等.可是我的牙痛等不了啊!